A Guide to the Wena Dows Architectural Collection, 1952-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Project Records (Map-case 35/Drawers 1-7)
  - Montrose, Jack and Doris ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-79; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Morantz/Sanchez ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-90; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Neidorf, R. ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-89; kitchen plan ) [ Dr ]
  - Newcomer, Barbara ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-76; addition to a duplex ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Newstadt/Kemp ( Winnetka; CA; Jul-01; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Newton, J./M.L. Middleton ( Woodland Hills; CA; May-90; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Newton, Susan ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Newton, Susan ( Los Angeles; CA; May-00; bath remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Niekirk, Sidney and Edna ( Calabasas Park; CA; Jan-80; master bedroom remodel ) Collaborator: Michael List Associates, Inerior designer [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Nomura, Art/Mary Daval ( Culver City; CA; Mar-99; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Notehelfer, F.G. ( Los Angeles; CA; May-05; dining room extension ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Nussbaum, Richard and Sheryl ( Tarzana; CA; Dec-94; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Nussbaum, Richard and Sheryl ( Tarzana; CA; Apr-92; portico addition ) [ Dr ]
  - O'Hara, Martin ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-76; patio cover, kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Oliva, Tony and Audrey ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Jan-99; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Olken ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-79; remodel [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Orlin, Lanny and Leah ( Hollywood; CA; Nov-76; remodeling, addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Ostrin, Ron and Leslie ( Culver City; CA; Jan-93; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - P+L Construction ( Redondo Beach; CA; Nov-89; 2 unit condo ) [ Dr ]
  - Paiva, Tom/Lee Draper ( Culver City; CA; Dec-02; addition; deck and spa ) [ Dr ]
  - Pannor, Harry and Joyce ( Los Angeles; CA; May-79; remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Parkhurst, David ( Glendale; CA; Mar-88; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Parkhurst, David ( Glendale; CA; Jun-84; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Parver, Mitchell and Karen ( Beverly Hills; CA; Apr-96; remodel, interior ) [ Dr ]
  - Parver, Mitchell and Karen ( Los Angeles; CA; March 1988, January 1987, June 1986, May 1981; remodel, addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Peardon, H. Bresler ( Woodland Hills; CA; Mar-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Pepper, Neal and Roz ( Encino; CA; 1978; deck and tellis ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Peter, Joan ( Santa Monica; CA; Oct-77; addition, remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Petersen, Rick and Carol ( Torrance; CA; Dec-02; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Pick, Charles and Gayle ( Hidden Hills; CA; Apr-00; addition, trellis replacement + extension ) [ Dr ]
  - Pitzer, John and Teri ( El Segundo; CA; Aug-00; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Plevy, Jay and Helen ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Porter, Jack and Myna ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-82; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Przelenski, Henry and Patricia ( Play del Ray; CA; Nov-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Rechtshaid, Marty ( Woodland Hills; CA; Nov-84; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Rechtshaid, Marty ( Woodland Hills; CA; Dec-80; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Reisler, Emil and Hanna ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-93; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Rice, Ed ( Rolling Hills Estate; CA; Sep-86; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rifkind, Bill and Erika ( Granada Hills; CA; Jun-95; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Roberts, Donald and Joanne ( Culver City; CA; Mar-82; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Robinson, Phillip and Jo ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-78; kitchen remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rogers, A. ( Beverly Hills; CA; Jul-75; remodeling, addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rogers, Arthur ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-88; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Rome, S. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-87; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rosen, Peter and Marla ( Beverly Hills; CA; Aug-95; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Rosenbloom, Barry and Beth ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rosenfelt, Fred and Nancy ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-81; addition ) Collaborator: Jim Marshall, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rosenthal, Angie ( Encino; CA; Jun-98; bath/closet remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Rowell, James and Eulene ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-78; 4 unit apartment building [not built?] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Rubinstein, Nathan and Ruth ( Beverly Hills; CA; Nov-83; residence ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph, Sl ]
  - Russell, Christopher and Arlene ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-83; addition ) Collaborator: Tim Skilton, contractor [ Ms, Dr, Ph, Sl ]
  - Rynew, Arden ( North Hollywood; CA; Mar-83; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Sackman, Gerry and Jessica ( Los Angeles; CA; May-91; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Sansone, Chistinia ( Glendale; CA; Apr-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Sauber, Tony and Sheila ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-02; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Schierholz, James ( Culver City; CA; Oct-86; addition ) Note: owner-built [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Schlessinger, Leonard and Phyllis ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Apr-81; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Schnitzer, Judy and Robert ( Los Angeles; CA; May-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Schulte, Jerry and Pamela ( Santa Monica; CA; Apr-83; garage/studio ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Schwebel, William and Mary Jane ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; May-83; second story ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Schwebel, William and Mary Jane ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; 1983; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Schwebel, William and Mary Jane ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; 1976; bath remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Service Data Processing, Aronoff Brothers Building, ( Van Nuys; CA; Aug-78; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Servis, Kenneth and Harriet ( Rolling Hills Estate; CA; Sep-98; deck/spa, landscape plan ) [ Dr ]
  - Servis, Kenneth and Harriet ( Rolling Hills Estate; CA; Jun-80; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Servis, Kenneth and Harriet ( Rolling Hills Estate; CA; Jan-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Shekelle, Paul and Elsa ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-00; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Shekelle, Paul and Elsa ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-98; kitchen remodel ) [ ]
  - Shekelle, Paul and Elsa ( Los Angeles; CA; May-94; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Shabsis, Howard ( Culver City; CA; Sep-77; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Shaffer, David ( Beverly Hills; CA; 1986; pool house addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Shaffer, David and Leila ( Beverly Hills; CA; Apr-85; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Shaffer, David and Leila ( Beverly Hills; CA; Apr-85; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Shinnick, Fred and Alice ( Culver City; CA; May-81; remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Short, Joe and Doris ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-74; addition, remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Shulman, Ira and Nadine ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-93; study plan, cabinets ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Shulman, Ira and Nadine ( Los Angeles; CA; May-88; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Shulman, Ira and Nadine ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-81; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Siegel, Carol ( Santa Monica P.O. (Los Angeles); CA; Sep-78; addition ) Collaborator: Steve LittleJohn, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Siegel, Carol ( Santa Monica P.O. (Los Angeles); CA; May-78; addition [not built] ) [ Dr ]
  - Siegel, Len and Pam ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-02; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Siegel, Len and Pam ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Siegel, Len and Pam ( Los Angeles; CA; May-90; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Siegel, Len and Pam ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-81; addition, remodel ) [ Ms, Ph ]
  - Siegel, Vicki ( Beverly Hills; CA; Feb-99; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Sigman, Harry ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Silk, Roger and Christine ( Sherman Oaks; CA; May-00; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Silk, Roger and Christine ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Sep-96; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Silvera, Rachel and Richard ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-84; kitchen, baths remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Singer, Lawrence ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-85; second story addition ) Collaborator: Don Johnson, contractor [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Singer, Lawrence ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-74; family room addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Siscoe, George/Nancy Crooker ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-84; addition; kitchen; dining room remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Skilton, Tim ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Smith, Bryce ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-96; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Smith, Leland and Talis ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-95; additions ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Sopher, Michael/Debbie Vilinsky ( Los Angeles; CA; May-02; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Sopher, Michael/Debbie Vilinsky ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-99; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Sperling, Harry and Kay ( Encino; CA; Jun-94; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Spiegel, Steve and Fredi ( Beverly Hills; CA; Mar-95; addition, remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Spiegel, Steve and Fredi ( Beverly Hills; CA; Jan-95; second floor addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Steinberg, Bernice ( Culver City; CA; Sep-94; garage remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Stephens, Phillip ( Los Angeles; CA; 1983, 1987; kitchen, bath remodels ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Stricke, Leslie and Stella ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Sussman, Karl ( Tarzana; CA; 1985-1986; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - SW corner Montana Ave + 7th Street ( Santa Monica; CA; Feb-95; commercial face lift ) [ Dr ]
  - Taylor, James ( Pacific Palisades; CA; May-82; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Tellez, Tony ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; Jul-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Thompson, Jack ( Topanga; CA; Aug-77; residence ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Thompson, Joan ( remodel ) [ Ms ]
  - Thompson, John L. ( Topanga; CA; Jan-81; residence [not built] ) [ Dr ]
  - Thompson, John M. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-81; second story addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Tobias, M./A. Simson ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Aug-92; deck ) [ Dr ]
  - Toledo/Walton ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-99; master bath, closet remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Topar, Philip and Candy ( El Segundo; CA; Aug-91; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Topar, Philip and Candy ( El Segundo; CA; Aug-91; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Traboulsi, Joseph ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Treister, Alan ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-88; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Unfrig, Jerome and Sue ( Beverly Hills; CA; Sep-78; deck, hot tub ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Unfrig, Jerome and Sue ( Beverly Hills; CA; Sep-77; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Unfrig/Caren ( Beverly Hills; CA; Mar-78; fence ) [ Dr ]
  - Upton, Christine ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-00; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Upton, Christine ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-00; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Valenzuela, Dan and Nancy ( Venice; CA; Mar-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Vener, Stuart and Bryna ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-79; second story addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Voyagis, Monique and Constantine ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-91; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Warshel, Arieh and Tamara ( Culver City; CA; Aug-85; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Watt, James J. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-66; garage ) [ Dr ]
  - Weaver, Jeffrey and Janice ( Culver City; CA; May-93; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Weigel, Jeffrey and Karen ( Los Angeles; CA; May-84; addition ) Collaborator: Juhn Muntz, contractor [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Weiman, Albert and Kathleen ( Hermosa Beach; CA; Sep-88; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Weiner, Harold ( Woodland Hills; CA; Dec-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Weiner, Larry and Janice ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-82; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Weiser, Stuart ( Beverly Hills; CA; Jan-84; revisions ) [ Dr ]
  - Weiser, Stuart ( Beverly Hills; CA; May-83; proposed 2nd story addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Weissman, Robert and Marim ( Tarzana; CA; Nov-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Weitzman, Marie and Bill ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-86; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Wells, Patty ( Hollywood; CA; Oct-82; residence [not built] ) [ Dr ]
  - Wells, Patty ( Hollywood; CA; May-81; addition [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Whitman, Gerald and Ricky ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-81; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Windman, Wayne ( Playa del Ray; CA; Aug-84; residence ) Collaborator: P&L Construction, contractor [ Ms, Dr, Sl ]
  - Wise, Doris ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Wittig, Curt and Michell ( Santa Monica; CA; 1979; patio cover ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Woods, Lesley/Richard McMurray ( Burbank; CA; May-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Wyers, Maxine ( Malibu; CA; May-83; residence ) [ Dr ]
  - Wynn, Michael and Susan ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-77; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Wynn, Philip and Judy ( Encino; CA; May-82; addition ) Collaborator: Jim Marshall, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Yang, Ron and Sharon ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-86; addition ) Collaborator: Eddie Glass, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Yang, Tien and Jane ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-79; second story addition ) [ Ms ]
  - Yi, Kang ( Venice; CA; Sep-82; remodel [incomplete, not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Yi, Kenneth (Kang) ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-78; addition - Hoagie's ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Ziering, Sigi ( Beverly Hills; CA; Jun-90; addition ) [ Dr ]